{"data":[{"question":"There were signs everywhere ________ people to keep out of the grass in the park.","a":"to tell","b":"tell","c":"telling","d":"to telling","answer":"3","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"It is very difficult ________ a twin from the other.","a":"tell","b":"to tell","c":"telling","d":"to telling","answer":"2","explain":"\n- It's + adj + to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"He is agreeable ________ to Nam's proposal.","a":"about","b":"to","c":"in","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be agreeable to sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"There are so many signs along that road ________ down because that road is very slippery.","a":"warning motorists to slow","b":"warn motorists to slow","c":"warn motorists slowing","d":"to warn motorists slowing","answer":"1","explain":"- We use present particle to shorten the relative clause","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Each of these sounds ________ me sleepy.","a":"make","b":"made","c":"makes","d":"has make","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject (Each of these sounds ) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Either Mike\u00a0or his friends ________ going to the beach today.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- If you use either-or\/ neither-nor\/not only- but also: look at the subject closest to the verb. If the subject closest to the verb is singular, use a singular verb; likewise, if the subject is plural, use a plural verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Everyone in the class ________ the novel.","a":"has read","b":"have read","c":"has red","d":"have red","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"He often ________ his dog when he comes home.","a":"whistles","b":"whistle","c":"is whistling","d":"are whistling","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express a habit (often).\u00a0\n- Subject (he) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"One of the golf clubs ________ in the corner of the room at this moment.","a":"stand","b":"stands","c":"is standing","d":"are standing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present Continuous: \n+Express the idea that something is happening now (at this moment).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary is doing her homework and ________ brother is helping her.","a":"she","b":"hers","c":"her","d":"she's","answer":"3","explain":"- Her: used as a possessive determiner followed by a noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}